Guide to the Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Curriculum and Student Data, 1938-1960; Series II
  - 1956-1957
    - Class schedules
      - Second quarter, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 65)
      - Third quarter, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 66)
      - Fourth quarter, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 67)
    - Quarter schedules, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 68)
    - Curriculum class schedule, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 69)
    - Course list, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 70-71)
    - Graduate School Course list, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 72)
    - "A concept of public health and trends as a basis for long term curriculum planning": report, 1951 (Box 354, Folder 73)
    - P.H.100 Preventive Medicine and Public Health, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 74-75)
    - P.H.101 Principles and practices of public health, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 76)
    - P.H. Sanitation of the Environment, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 77)
    - P.H. Community Organization and Problems, 1956-1957 (Box 354, Folder 78)
    - P.H.101 and 121 Psychiatry in Relation to Public Health, 1956-1957 (Box 355, Folder 79-80)
    - P.H.101 Public Health Education, 1956-1957 (Box 355, Folder 81-85)
    - "Avoid spreading colds": newspaper clipping, undated (Box 355, Folder 86)
    - P.H.101 Epidemiological Methods, communicable Disease Control, 1956-1957 (Box 355, Folder 87)
    - P.H.101 and 119 Nutrition, 1956-1957 (Box 355, Folder 88)
    - P.H.101 and 117 Maternal and Child Health, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 89)
    - P.H.101 and 106 Physiological Hygiene, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 90)
    - P.H.102a Principles of Vital Statistics, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 91)
    - P.H.102b Public Health Statistics, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 92)
    - P.H.103e Statistical Methods in Medical Research, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 93)
    - P.H.105 Public Health Seminar, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 94-95)
    - P.H.107 Elements in Public Health Engineering, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 96)
    - P.H.109 Public Health Education, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 97-98)
    - P.H.110a Social Aspects of Medicine, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 99)
    - P.H.111 School Health, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 100)
    - P.H.114 Health Administration, 1956-1957 (Box 356, Folder 101-102)
    - P.H.114 Health Administration, 1956-1957 (Box 357, Folder 103-105)
    - P.H.115 Principles of Epidemiology, 1956-1957 (Box 357, Folder 106)
    - P.H.116 Human Ecology, 1956-1957 (Box 357, Folder 107)
    - P.H.118 Medical Jurisprudence, 1956-1957 (Box 357, Folder 108)
    - P.H.120 Public Health Law, 1956-1957 (Box 357, Folder 109)
    - P.H.122 Medical Care in Modern Society, 1956-1957 (Box 357, Folder 110)
    - Economics of Medical Practice Invitations, replies, programs and texts, 1956-1957 (Box 357, Folder 111-113)
    - P.H.123 Hygiene of Housing, 1956-1957 (Box 358, Folder 114)
    - Medical Jurisprudence, 1956-1957 (Box 358, Folder 115)
    - P.H.130-137 Principles and Practices of Cancer Control, 1956-1957 (Box 358, Folder 116)
    - P.H.150-159 Occupational Health Program, 1956-1957 (Box 358, Folder 117)
    - Economics of Medical Care, 1956-1957 (Box 358, Folder 118-120)
    - Occupational Health, 1956-1957 (Box 358, Folder 121)
    - Post-occupational Health, 1956-1957 (Box 358, Folder 122)
    - Hospital Administration Program, 1956-1957 (Box 358, Folder 123)
  - 1957-1958
    - Application fees, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 124)
    - General student correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 125)
    - Student data, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 126)
    - Student medical insurance, 1957 (Box 359, Folder 127)
    - Student registration, 1957 (Box 359, Folder 128)
    - Field trips, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 129)
    - Grades, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 130-131)
    - Guest lecturers, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 132)
    - Student lists, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 133-135)
    - Student reports, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 136)
    - Tuition lists, 1957-1958 (Box 359, Folder 137)
    - Student reports, 1950-1956 (Box 360, Folder 138-140)
    - Withdrawals and rejections
      - A - G, 1957-1958 (Box 360, Folder 141-142)
      - A - G, 1957-1958 (Box 360, Folder 143-146)
      - H - Z, 1957-1958 (Box 360, Folder 147-149)
      - H - Z, 1957-1958 (Box 360, Folder 150-151)
      - H - Z, 1957-1958 (Box 361, Folder 152-153)
    - USPHS Title 1: Yale traineeship O"Connor, John F., (58-104), 1958 (Box 361, Folder 154)
    - Inquiries
      - January, 1957-1958 (Box 361, Folder 155-156)
      - February, 1957-1958 (Box 361, Folder 157-159)
      - March, 1957-1958 (Box 361, Folder 160-162)
      - April, 1957-1958 (Box 361, Folder 163-165)
      - May, 1957-1958 (Box 361, Folder 166)
      - June, 1957-1958 (Box 362, Folder 167)
      - July, 1957-1958 (Box 362, Folder 168)
      - August, 1957-1958 (Box 362, Folder 169)
      - September, 1957-1958 (Box 362, Folder 170-171)
      - October, 1957-1958 (Box 362, Folder 172)
      - November, 1957-1958 (Box 362, Folder 173)
      - December, 1957-1958 (Box 362, Folder 174-175)
    - Other than student inquiries, 1957-1958 (Box 362, Folder 176)
  - 1957-1958
    - Book lists, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 177)
    - Class schedule: medical school, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 178)
    - Class schedule: nursing school, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 179)
    - Class schedules: first quarter, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 180)
    - P.H.102a Principles of Vital Statistics, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 181-182)
    - Class schedules: second quarter, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 183)
    - Class schedules: third quarter, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 184)
    - Class schedules: fourth quarter, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 185)
    - Quarter schedules, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 186)
    - Course lists, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 187-189)
    - General seminar, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 190)
    - P.H.100 Preventive Medicine and Public Health, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 191)
    - P.H.100 External Medicine, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 192)
    - P.H.101 Sanitation of the Environment, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 193)
    - P.H.101 Community Organization and Problems, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 194)
    - P.H.101 and 121 Psychiatry in Relation to Public Health, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 195)
    - P.H.101 Public Health Education, 1957-1958 (Box 363, Folder 196-197)
    - P.H.101 Public Health Education, 1957-1958 (Box 364, Folder 198)
    - P.H.101 Epidemiological Methods of Communicable Disease Control, 1957-1958 (Box 364, Folder 199)
    - P.H.101 and 119 Nutrition, 1957-1958 (Box 364, Folder 200)
    - P.H.101 and 117 Maternal and Child Health, 1957-1958 (Box 364, Folder 201)
    - P.H.101 and 106 Physiological Hygiene, 1957-1958 (Box 364, Folder 202)
    - P.H.102a and 102b Public Health Statistics, 1957-1958 (Box 364, Folder 203)
    - P.H.103d Statistical Epidemiology, 1957-1958 (Box 364, Folder 204)
    - P.H.105 Public Health Seminar, 1957-1958 (Box 364, Folder 205-210)
    - P.H.107 Elements in Public Health Engineering, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 211)
    - P.H.109 Public Health Education, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 212-215)
    - P.H.110b Problems of Medical Care Administration, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 216)
    - P.H.111 School Health, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 217)
    - P.H.112 Heart Disease Control, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 218)
    - P.H.113 Public Health Nursing, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 219)
    - P.H.114 public Health Administration, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 220-222)
    - P.H.115 Principles of Epidemiology, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 223-224)
    - P.H.118 Medical Jurisprudence, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 225)
    - Legal medicine, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 226)
    - P.H.120 Public Health Law, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 227)
    - P.H.125 Hospital Clinics, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 228)
    - P.H.130-137 Principles and Practices of Cancer Control, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 229)
    - P.H.150-159 Occupational Health Program, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 230)
    - Occupational health, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 231)
    - Hospital administration program, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 232)
    - Seminar schedule, 1957-1958 (Box 365, Folder 233)
  - 1958-1959
    - Application fees, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 234)
    - Student applications for admission, 1959 (Box 366, Folder 235)
    - Student addresses (M.P.H.), 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 236)
    - Student data, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 237)
    - Essay requirements, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 238)
    - Notification of foreign student acceptance, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 239)
    - Prospective student history forms, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 240)
    - Student information blank, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 241)
    - Forms for student evaluation remarks, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 242)
    - Form for recording credentials, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 243)
    - Face sheets, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 244)
    - Advisor"s evaluation of student forms, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 246)
    - Committee on admissions form, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 247)
    - Blank course schedule, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 248)
    - Grades, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 249-250)
    - Graduate student information, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 251-253)
    - Guest lecturers, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 254)
    - Resident faculty member list, 1958-1959 (Box 366, Folder 255)
    - Secretary staff list, 1958-1959 (Box 367, Folder 256)
    - Medical School: students registered in other departments, 1958-1959 (Box 367, Folder 257)
    - Tuition lists, 1958-1959 (Box 367, Folder 258)
    - Withdrawals and rejections
      - A - G (Box 367, Folder 259-260)
      - H - Z, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 261-264)
    - Inquiries
      - January, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 265-268)
      - February, 1958-1959 (Box 368, Folder 269-271)
      - March, 1958-1959 (Box 368, Folder 272-274)
      - April, 1958-1959 (Box 368, Folder 275-277)
      - May, 1958-1959 (Box 368, Folder 278)
      - June, 1958-1959 (Box 368, Folder 279)
      - July, 1958-1959 (Box 368, Folder 280)
      - August, 1958-1959 (Box 368, Folder 281)
      - September, 1958-1959 (Box 368, Folder 282-283)
      - September, 1958-1959 (Box 369, Folder 284)
      - October, 1958-1959 (Box 369, Folder 285-287)
      - November, 1958-1959 (Box 369, Folder 288-289)
      - December, 1958-1959 (Box 369, Folder 290-291)
  - 1958-1959
    - Class schedules
      - First quarter, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 292)
      - Second quarter, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 293)
      - Fourth quarter, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 294)
    - Course list, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 295-297)
    - P.H.100 Preventive Medicine and Public Health, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 298-299)
    - P.H.100 Principles and Practices of Public Health, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 300)
    - P.H.101 Sanitation of the Environment, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 301)
    - P.H.101 Community Organization and Problems, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 302-303)
    - P.H.101 Community Organization and Problems, 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 304)
    - P.H.101 and 121 Psychiatry in Relation to Public Health, 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 305)
    - P.H.101 Public Health Education, 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 306-308)
    - P.H.101 E.M.C.D.C., 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 309)
    - P.H.101 and 117 Maternal and Child Health, 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 310)
    - P.H.101 and 106 Physiological Hygiene, 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 311)
    - P.H.102a Principles of Vital Statistics, 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 312-314)
    - P.H.102b Public Health Statistics, 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 315)
    - P.H.103b Statistical Epidemiology, 1958-1959 (Box 371, Folder 316)
    - P.H.103e Statistical Methods in Medical Research, 1958-1959 (Box 372, Folder 317-319)
    - P.H.105 Public Health Seminar (2nd semester), 1958-1959 (Box 372, Folder 320-323)
    - P.H.105 Public Health Seminar, 1958-1959 (Box 372, Folder 324-326)
    - P.H.107 Elements in Public Health Engineering, 1958-1959 (Box 372, Folder 327)
    - P.H.109 Public Health Education, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 328-329)
    - P.H.110b Problems of Medical Care Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 330)
    - P.H.111 School Health, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 331)
    - P.H.113 Public Health Nursing, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 332-333)
    - P.H.114 Public Health Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 334-335)
    - P.H.115 Principles of Epidemiology, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 336)
    - P.H.120 Public Health Law, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 337-338)
    - P.H.122 Medical Care in Modern Society, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 339)
    - P.H.123 Hygiene of Housing, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 340)
    - P.H.130-137 Principles and Practices of Cancer Control, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 341-342)
    - Economics of medical care, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 343)
    - Hospital administration program, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 344)
    - Seminar schedule, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 345)
    - Submarine sessions, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 346)
    - Radiology: medical school, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 347)
    - P.H.101 Evaluation of a special session for international students, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 348)
  - Student Data 1959-1960
    - Admissions, Committee on, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 349)
    - Application fees, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 350)
    - Applications for admission, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 351)
    - Forms: student evaluation remarks, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 352)
    - Forms: post office report form and mailing list for catalogues, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 353)
    - Graduate records: blank letters, questionaires, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 354)
    - Course grade charts, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 355)
    - Course grades, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 356-357)
    - Voucher forms: ICA students (department H, E, W), 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 358)
    - International Cooperation Administration, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 359)
    - Medical students, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 360)
    - Special students, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 361)
    - Tuition lists, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 362)
    - Withdrawals and rejections
      - A - B, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 363-365)
      - C - E, 1959-1960 (Box 375, Folder 366)
      - C - F, 1959-1960 (Box 376, Folder 367-368)
      - G - J, 1959-1960 (Box 376, Folder 369-370)
      - K, 1959-1960 (Box 376, Folder 371-372)
      - L, 1959-1960 (Box 376, Folder 373)
      - K - M, 1959-1960 (Box 376, Folder 374-375)
      - N - Q, 1959-1960 (Box 376, Folder 376)
      - R - T, 1959-1960 (Box 376, Folder 377-378)
      - U - Z, 1959-1960 (Box 377, Folder 379)
    - Inquiries
      - January, 1959-1960 (Box 377, Folder 380-381)
      - February, 1959-1960 (Box 377, Folder 382-383)
      - March, 1959-1960 (Box 377, Folder 384-386)
      - April, 1959-1960 (Box 377, Folder 387-388)
      - May, 1959-1960 (Box 377, Folder 389)
      - June, 1959-1960 (Box 377, Folder 390)
      - July, 1959-1960 (Box 377, Folder 391)
      - August, 1959-1960 (Box 378, Folder 392)
      - September, 1959-1960 (Box 378, Folder 393-394)
      - October, 1959-1960 (Box 378, Folder 395)
      - November, 1959-1960 (Box 378, Folder 396-397)
      - December, 1959-1960 (Box 378, Folder 398)
      - Class schedules: all quarters, 1959-1960 (Box 378, Folder 399)
    - School of Medicine: P.H.101 Preventive Medicine and Public Health Dr. Paul, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 400)
    - Preventive medicine: questions, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 401)
    - P.H.101 Principles and Practices of Public Health, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 402)
    - P.H.101 Sanitation of the Environment, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 403)
    - P.H.101 Community Organization of Problems, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 404)
    - P.H.101 Public Health Education, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 405-406)
    - P.H.101 Nutrition, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 407)
    - P.H.101 Maternal and Child Health, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 408)
    - P.H.101 Mental Health, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 409)
    - P.H.101 Epidemiology and Communicable Disease Control, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 410)
    - Epidemiology progress report, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 411)
    - P.H.101 Physiological Hygiene, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 412)
    - P.H.101 Concepts of Public Health, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 413)
    - P.H.101 Questionaire, 1959-1960 (Box 379, Folder 414)
    - P.H.105 Public Health Seminar, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 415)
    - P.H.108 Sanitation of the Environment, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 416)
    - P.H.109 Public Health Education, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 417)
    - P.H.111 School Health, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 418)
    - P.H.113 Public Health Nursing, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 419)
    - P.H.115 Principles of Epidemiology, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 420)
    - P.H.123 Hygiene of Housing, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 421)
    - P.H.126 Adult Health, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 422)
    - P.H.127 Chronic Illness Nursing, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 423)
    - P.H.160 Special: organizational behavior, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 424)
    - P.H.160 Hospital Administration Program, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 425)
    - Community mental health seminar, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 426)
    - Community program for retarded children, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 427)
    - Hospital law, 1959-1960 (Box 380, Folder 428)
    - General public health seminar: radiation hazards, 1960 (Box 380, Folder 429)
- Surveys, 1924-1958; Series III
  - Akron, Ohio, 1947-1948 (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1942 (Box 381, Folder 2-6)
  - Bristol, Connecticut
    - Administration, undated (Box 381, Folder 7)
    - Community Organization and Health Education, 1957 (Box 381, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 381, Folder 9)
    - Directories of Key and professional people, 1957 (Box 382, Folder 10)
    - Environmental sanitation, 1955-1957 (Box 382, Folder 11)
    - Expense accounts, finances, 1957 (Box 382, Folder 12)
    - Forms, questionnaires, schedules, 1957 (Box 382, Folder 13)
    - Hospitals, 1957 (Box 382, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 382, Folder 15-16)
    - Nursing, 1957-1958 (Box 382, Folder 17)
    - Occupational health, 1957 (Box 382, Folder 18)
    - Reports, 1957 (Box 382, Folder 19-21)
    - Reports, 1957 (Box 383, Folder 22)
    - School health, 1957-1958 (Box 383, Folder 23)
    - Statistics, 1957 (Box 383, Folder 24)
    - Tuberculosis control, 1957 (Box 383, Folder 25)
  - Canton, Ohio, 1947 (Box 383, Folder 26-28)
  - Columbus, Ohio, 1942-1955 (Box 384, Folder 29)
  - Columbus, Ohio, 1953-1954 (Box 384, Folder 30-32)
  - Darien, Connecticut
    - 1948 (Box 384, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 384, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 385, Folder 35-36)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1954-1956 (Box 385, Folder 37)
    - Reports, 1954-1957 (Box 385, Folder 38)
    - School Health Program: Dr. Charles C. Wilson, 1949-1954 (Box 385, Folder 39)
    - General statistics, 1955-1956 (Box 385, Folder 40)
  - Eastern Windham County, 1957-1958 (Box 386, Folder 41-42)
    - Directories of key people, 1958 (Box 386, Folder 43)
    - Environmental sanitation, 1958 (Box 386, Folder 44)
    - Expense accounts and finances, 1957-1958 (Box 386, Folder 45)
    - Reports, general, 1957-1958 (Box 386, Folder 46-48)
    - Request letters, 1957 (Box 386, Folder 49)
    - Schedule for community health study, 1957-1958 (Box 387, Folder 50)
    - Schedules for community health study, 1958 (Box 387, Folder 51)
    - School health, 1957-1958 (Box 387, Folder 52-53)
    - Statistics, general, 1957-1958 (Box 387, Folder 54)
    - Ashford, Connecticut, 1950-1957 (Box 387, Folder 55)
    - Canterbury, Connecticut, 1947-1957 (Box 388, Folder 56)
    - Chaplin, Connecticut, 1950-1957 (Box 388, Folder 57)
    - Danielson, Connecticut (Box 388, Folder 58)
    - Eastford, Connecticut, 1950-1957 (Box 388, Folder 59)
    - Killingly, Connecticut, 1950, 1957 (Box 388, Folder 60)
    - Moosup, Connecticut, 1958 (Box 388, Folder 61)
    - Plainfield, Connecticut, 1956-1957 (Box 388, Folder 62)
    - Putnam, Connecticut, 1958-1959 (Box 388, Folder 63-65)
    - Pomfret, Connecticut, 1953-1957 (Box 389, Folder 66)
    - Sterling, Connecticut, 1953, 1956, 1957 (Box 389, Folder 67)
    - Thompson, Connecticut, 1950, 1957 (Box 389, Folder 68)
    - Woodstock, Connecticut, 1950-1957 (Box 389, Folder 69)
  - Greenwich, Connecticut
    - Printed matter, 1954 (Box 390, Folder 70A-B)
    - Printed matter, 1954 (Box 390, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence, general, 1954 (Box 390, Folder 72-73)
    - Miscellaneous data, 1954 (Box 390, Folder 74-75)
  - Hartford, Connecticut
    - Bulletins and other pertinent material, 1954-1955 (Box 390, Folder 76)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 391, Folder 77-79)
    - Hospital data, 1954-1956 (Box 391, Folder 80)
    - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 391, Folder 81)
    - Muller's folder: "Needs Summary" Interview reports, Hartford Rehabilitation Center data, 1956 (Box 391, Folder 82)
    - Public Health Nursing Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 392, Folder 83-85)
    - Reports and statistics, 1954-1956 (Box 392, Folder 86-87)
    - Reports and statistics, 1954-1956 (Box 393, Folder 88-90)
    - Special comments and progress notes, 1956 (Box 393, Folder 91)
    - Subcommittee on Medical Care, 1956 (Box 393, Folder 92)
  - East Hartford, Connecticut
    - Administration, 1957 (Box 393, Folder 93)
    - Adult health and rehabilitation, 1957 (Box 393, Folder 94)
    - Bulletins, 1957 (Box 393, Folder 95)
    - Community organization and health education, 1957 (Box 393, Folder 96)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 393, Folder 98)
    - Dental care, 1957-1958 (Box 394, Folder 99)
    - Directories of key people (Box 394, Folder 100)
    - Bosworth, Karl A., 1956 (Box 394, Folder 101)
    - Environmental sanitation, 1957-1958 (Box 394, Folder 102)
    - Expense accounts, finances, 1957-1958 (Box 394, Folder 103)
    - Forms, questionnaires, schedules, 1957 (Box 394, Folder 104)
    - Hospitals, 1957-1958 (Box 394, Folder 105)
    - Laws and regulations concerning, public health, 1957 (Box 394, Folder 106)
    - Maternal and child health, 1957-1958 (Box 394, Folder 107)
    - Mental health, 1957-1958 (Box 394, Folder 108)
    - Needs for beds and chronic illness, 1956 (Box 394, Folder 109)
    - Nursing, 1958 (Box 394, Folder 110)
    - Occupational health, 1957 (Box 394, Folder 111)
    - Publicity, 1957 (Box 394, Folder 112)
    - Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 395, Folder 113-119)
    - Request letters, 1957 (Box 395, Folder 120)
    - School health, 1957-1958 (Box 396, Folder 121)
    - Statistics, 1953-1957 (Box 396, Folder 122)
    - Tuberculosis control, 1957 (Box 396, Folder 123)
  - West Hartford, Connecticut
    - Clinics, 1956-1957 (Box 396, Folder 124)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 396, Folder 125)
    - Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 396, Folder 126)
    - Nursing, 1956 (Box 396, Folder 127)
    - Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 396, Folder 128)
    - School health: Charles C. Wilson, 1956-1957 (Box 396, Folder 129)
    - Statistics, general, 1956 (Box 396, Folder 130)
  - Naugatuck Valley
    - Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 397, Folder 131)
    - General material relating to the survey, 1957 (Box 397, Folder 132)
    - General material relating to the survey, 1955-1957 (Box 397, Folder 133-134)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1954-1957 (Box 397, Folder 135)
    - Reports, 1954-1957 (Box 397, Folder 136-137)
    - Statistics, 1954-1957 (Box 398, Folder 138)
    - Ansonia, Connecticut, 1954-1957 (Box 398, Folder 139)
    - Derby, Connecticut, 1954-1957 (Box 398, Folder 140)
    - Oxford, Connecticut, 1954-1957 (Box 398, Folder 141)
    - Seymour, Connecticut, 1954-1957 (Box 398, Folder 142)
    - Shelton, Connecticut, 1953-1956 (Box 398, Folder 143)
  - New Canaan, Connecticut, 1947-1948 (Box 398, Folder 144)